<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jet&#39;s Desk</title>
    <link>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jet&#39;s Desk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2023, JetGirl.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 22:24:16 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tellinstories</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/tellinstories/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 22:24:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/tellinstories/</guid>
      <description>This is a page about »Tellinstories«.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Nugget</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/new-nugget/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:17:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/new-nugget/</guid>
      <description>I got a new music nugget last week. For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know I like to listen to music separate from my phone. This is due to all the spam calls and notifications I get on my main device that make listening to music or podcasts difficult with all the constant interrupts.
During the pandemic I picked up a couple of broken Zunes and fixed them up to listen to offline music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Updates</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/garden-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 01:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/garden-updates/</guid>
      <description>Hey, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy around here. Getting the garden ready is taking longer than expected due to rain and time logistics. (I have about a two hour window during the day when the baby sleeps to do outside stuff.)
I also wanted to see if the photos I uploaded would work. Here is the first one which is the raised beds I assembled.
They are the 3ft tall and 17 inch tall raised beds by Vego Garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Plans</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/garden-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 12:20:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/garden-plans/</guid>
      <description>So our new house has a massive back yard which has more than enough room to grow a garden. The previous owners had attempted such in the back corner by tilling up a 12 x 12 area of dirt and putting down black plastic to grow something.
I know they attempted cow peas and some tiny peppers because that&amp;rsquo;s all that was left, burned to a crisp when we bought the place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Plot Just Vibes</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/no-plot-just-vibes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 14:27:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/no-plot-just-vibes/</guid>
      <description>I like stories where &amp;ldquo;nothing happens&amp;rdquo;. Where I&amp;rsquo;m not &amp;ldquo;hooked&amp;rdquo; in the first sentence with little plot treats like a puppy. I don&amp;rsquo;t need the villain to be redeemable or the hero to be relatable. That last bit will become contradictory in a sec just wait you can point at it later and call me an idiot that&amp;rsquo;s fine.
I like the stories where I&amp;rsquo;m slowly lowered into a setting before being shoved into the action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Museum</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/the-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 19:03:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/the-museum/</guid>
      <description>I like going to art museums. Back in school, we would often visit galleries around town typically for a juried show. My stuff never made it in any of them but I went to see my classmates work. But galleries are typically designed to sell the works, and you won&amp;rsquo;t see the same show on the walls twice.
Museums on the other hand all have a permanent collection, owned by the org itself or perpetually on loan from a collector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seinfeld&#39;s Stale Cereal</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/seinfelds-stale-cereal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:48:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/seinfelds-stale-cereal/</guid>
      <description>Two years ago we started watching Seinfeld as a background show when Netflix lost The Office. That Christmas I got the Lego version of the Seinfeld apartment. It only took a few hours to build but it came with so many little details from the show - including the kitchen and the row of cereal boxes.
For those who haven&amp;rsquo;t ever watched Seinfeld, Jerry&amp;rsquo;s kitchen has an entire shelf above his sink dedicated to about nine boxes of cereal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogroll</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/blogroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 23:59:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/blogroll/</guid>
      <description>Blogroll Every blog worth its salt has a blogroll.
Matt Bell Lincoln Michel G. Michael Rapp Craig Foster Brandon Taylor If we don&amp;rsquo;t get no tolls, then we don&amp;rsquo;t eat no rolls.
Want to have your site listed above? Shoot me an email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 23:59:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Digital Email
Twitter
Postcards PO BOX 1046 Mineola, TX 75773
Donate Buy Me A Coffee
Amazon Wishlist ETH 0x32b23f1628d56863775814DEF201Ed5BE5Ba8fdc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial Commit</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/initial-commit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 23:59:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jetgirl.art/jetsdesk/initial-commit/</guid>
      <description>Yeah so if after a year your email list is the same size it&amp;rsquo;s a safe bet to move on. Every single marketing tactic says you need to build an email list and maintain a newsletter to keep your readers engaged and network with other authors.
The issue with that is your readers aren&amp;rsquo;t just reading you. They are subscribed to thirty other newsletters and even with Substack&amp;rsquo;s app it can be hard to keep up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
